let questions = [
  {
    number: 1,
    question:
      "From which platform at Kings Cross does the Hogwarts Express train depart? ",
    options: [
      "Gringotts",
      "Wand",
      "Nine and three quarters",
      "The trolls club",
    ],
    answer: "Nine and three quarters",
  },
  {
    number: 2,
    question: "Harry has a scar on his forehead. What shape is it?",
    options: [
      "Like a horse tail",
      "Like a lightning bolt",
      "Like a shining star",
      "Like an egg",
    ],
    answer: "Like a lightning bolt",
  },
  {
    number: 3,
    question: "Harrys uncle and aunt, the Dursleys, live at what address? ",
    options: [
      "Number 4, Privet Drive",
      "Hogwarts",
      "The trolls club",
      "Muggle Mansion",
    ],
    answer: "Number 4, Privet Drive",
  },
  {
    number: 4,
    question: "Hermiones parents are not wizards. What non-wizard jobs do they do? ",
    options: [
      "Physician",
      "Tailor",
      "Dentists",
      "Mechanic",
    ],
    answer: "Dentists",
  },
  {
    number: 5,
    question: "How do the Dursleys say that Harrys parents died? ",
    options: [
      "In a car crash",
      "In a aeroplane crash",
      "By Cancer",
      "By Heart Attack",
    ],
    answer: "In a car crash",
  },
  {
    number: 6,
    question: "How old was Voldemort when he opened the Chamber of Secrets?  ",
    options: [
      "12 years",
      "15 years",
      "16 years",
      "11 years",
    ],
    answer: "16 years",
  },
  {
    number: 7,
    question: "In Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone, who reports the commentary for the Quidditch matches at Hogwarts? ",
    options: [
      "Albus Dumbledore",
      "Lee Jordan",
      "Mrs Norris",
      "Professor Sprout",
    ],
    answer: "Lee Jordan",
  },
  {
    number: 8,
    question: "In which year (1-7) did Harry go on his first date with Cho Chang? ",
    options: [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5",
    ],
    answer: "5",
  },
  {
    number: 9,
    question: "On a Quidditch pitch, how many goal posts are there in total? ",
    options: [
      "Four",
      "Five",
      "Six",
      "Seven",
    ],
    answer: "Six",
  },
  {
    number: 10,
    question: "On which object does Ron cast Wingardium Leviosa when in the girls bathroom? ",
    options: [
      "Wand",
      "The trolls club",
      "A hat",
      "The tap",
    ],
    answer: "The trolls club",
  },
  {
    number: 11,
    question: "To cast a spell you need to say specific words whilst holding which type of magical object? ",
    options: [
      "A mirror",
      "A Wand",
      "A Pot",
      "A ball",
    ],
    answer: "A Wand",
  },
  {
    number: 12,
    question: "What gift does Hagrid give Harry in Diagon Alley? ",
    options: [
      "An Owl",
      "A cat",
      "A horse",
      "A wand",
    ],
    answer: "An Owl",
  },
];
